STANDARD FOR LIFE
NOTE: The footage you are about to watch may not be suitable for all viewers.
Although it is of a sensitive nature, it is for the glory of God and to build your faith.
♪ Who is in the house? God is in the house. G.O.D. God is in the house -♪
♪ through His Word. Yeah. Are you in the very house? G.O.D.♪
Here we can see Mrs Olaitan Olomo
who came to The Synagogue Church of All Nations, Lagos, Nigeria,
with the problem of jaundice that affected the baby's breathing.
She knew that the baby had stopped breathing, and the doctor later confirmed this to be true.
Mrs Olaitan has been arranged for prayer due to the sickness which has affected her pregnancy.
The man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, has just begun to pray.
♪ Let my heart be...♪
Prophet T.B. Joshua is now praying for Mrs Olaitan.
♪ Let my spirit feel the warmth of Your embrace.♪
♪ Let me be...♪
The baby is turning, and is turning to take a right position.
No, no, no! Cover her, cover her!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
See what the Lord has done!
♪ Yeah. God is in the house! Come on... The Bible calls the church a house where God lives... Yeah, Yeah, Yeah! ♪
♪ God is in the house! Alright! God is in the house! Through His Word. Are you, in the very house?♪
Glory be to God! Your miracle can be in a moment.
As the man of God spoke the Word of faith,
the baby was delivered instantly,
right there on the spot,
in the midst of the crowd
and the placenta came out immediately.
God is indeed the miracle provider.
♪ The bible calls the church. Yeah, Yeah, Yeah, Yeah, Yeah! A house where God lives. Who is in the house?♪
♪ God is in the house. G.O.D! God is in the house... in the house... through His Word.♪
♪ Are you, in the very house? Tell me one more time.♪
♪ God is in the house. OH YES! God is in the house, through His Word.♪
Emmanuel!
Emmanuel!!! God With Us (Matthew 1:23)
My name is Olaitan Olomo.
I came to The Synagogue, Church of All Nations with the problem of jaundice.
My sickness was very severe.
I went to different doctors for solution, but all to no avail.
The doctor said that the jaundice affected the baby's breathing in my womb.
I told my mother, and she directed me here to
The Synagogue, Church of All Nations.
When I came to The Synagogue, Church of All Nations,
I was arranged at the emergency section of the prayer line of the church.
Immediately Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me, the baby was
revived and started turning to its normal position.
Instantly, the baby came out with ease. Praise the Lord!
Emmanuel! Emmanuel! Emmanuel! God With Us (Matthew 1:23)
I thank Almighty God for using Prophet T.B. Joshua for the safe delivery of my baby.
I am alive, and my baby is alive.
My baby can breathe, eat, cry and do everything a normal baby can do!
3 years after she was delivered of her baby in The Synagogue Church of All Nations, Lagos, Nigeria,
Mrs Olomo came back to the Church with her child
to testify about the miraculous birth of the very child.
♪ God is in the house. G.O.D! God is in the house... in the house... through His Word.♪
♪ Are you, in the very house? G.O.D in the house. God is in the house through His Word.♪
♪ Are you in the very house?♪
♪ Take it from me one more time. The Bible calls the church...♪
About three years ago, she came to The Synagogue Church of All Nations
with the problem of jaundice, unsafe delivery.
and she was placed at the prayer line where the anointed man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua,
prayed for her and she said, instantly the man of God stretched forth his hand
towards her she started feeling the kicking of the baby
and she delivered her baby instantly right there at the prayer line
and that was almost three years ago.
She is here today with a little baby named Mary.
What is your name?
Mary.
How are you?
Fine, thank you.
She said, She is fine, and you can see the mother and the child
thanking God Almighty for what the Lord has done.
We give glory to God!
♪ The Bible calls the church. Yeah Yeah Yeah Yea♪ h!!
♪ The house where God lives. Who is in the house?♪
♪ God is in the house. G.O.D. God is in the house... in the house... through His Word.♪
♪ Emmanuel!♪ God!♪
♪ With Us!♪
♪ Emmanuel! God With Us♪
♪ Emmanuel! God With Us!♪
The SCOAN Saturday Prayer Line
Hallelujah!
You've heard the wonderful testimony of this woman
who came to The Synagogue Church of All of Nations prayer line.
And she was here with the problem of safe delivery. She had a problem of jaundice.
And as a result of that problem of jaundice, the child was unable
to breathe in her womb. She said that it was her mother
that recommended her to come to The Synagogue Church of All Nations
because before that the doctor had actually said that she should be operated.
So she came to The Synagogue Church of All Nations
and we saw exactly what took place. Instantly, as the man of God
stretched forth his hand and prayed for her, the baby came out instantly,
followed very shortly by the placenta. The baby that previously was not breathing
came out alive and this is the very child that we can see standing
before us called Mary.
Let us put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
Now, if you noticed in the previous interview, our sister was speaking in her local language
and right now we want to give her the freedom to express herself freely
and give her the opportunity to express herself in her local language.
My name is Olaitan Olomo.
Ten years ago, I had the problem of jaundice and was very sick.
"She said that her name is Mrs Olaitan Olomo.Ten years ago, she came to The Synagogue Church of All Nations"
for the very first time with the terrible problem of jaundice in her life.
Then, I was pregnant and at the same time I was sick with jaundice.
So, the baby in my womb was not breathing as a result of this.
She said that when she had this problem of jaundice, she was heavily pregnant
but the baby in her womb stopped breathing, stopped moving.
The baby stopped moving; so, I was afraid.
I knew something was wrong with my baby.
I suspected that the baby no longer moves, no longer breathes.
Then, I went to see my doctor who told me that my baby was no longer moving
nor breathing and that the only alternative was for me to be operated on.
So, when I went to the doctor, the doctor confirmed that truly the baby had become lifeless in my womb
and the doctor recommended an operation,
that is, the baby was to be taken out of my womb through operation
because the baby was no longer moving, no longer breathing.
I was an unbeliever then; I didn't even know who Jesus was.
So she said that as at that time, she did not know who Jesus Christ was.
She had never been to any church. She had not given her life to God.
It was my mother who was a member of The SCOAN.
But my mother was a member of Synagogue Church of All Nations at that time.
I told my mother that the doctor said that the only remedy for me
was to be operated on. She said that I would never be operated on.
So, when she mentioned the issue of operation to her mother
her mother said, No! By the grace of God, you will not do any operation.
My mother asked me to come to The SCOAN
and when I came, I was placed on the prayer line.
So, the mother recommended that she came to The Synagogue Church of All Nations
and the moment she came, she was placed at the prayer line.
While I was sitting down at the prayer line,
the man of God came and stretched his right hand towards me
and prayed for me.
So, whilst I was placed at the prayer line, the anointed man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, came.
As he was praying for the people he came right in front of me
and stretched forth his hand towards me and started praying.
Immediately, the baby in my womb turned, and I fell into labour.
Instantly, as the man of God was offering the prayer in the name of Jesus Christ
the baby that had been lifeless, the baby that had stopped breathing in my womb,
that had died in my womb turned immediately.
As the baby in my womb turned,
the man of God said the baby was taking the right position
because the baby was not breathing previously.
So, the man of God himself confirmed at that spot that the baby had now positioned in the proper way in the womb.
Instantly after the prayer, I went into labour and delivered my baby
right here at the prayer line where I am testifying.
So, immediately the anointed man of God stretched forth his hand
and said, In the Name of Jesus Christ, you will deliver this baby right now.
She said that she lost control of herself and all she knew was that she delivered
her baby instantly right here at the prayer line section. The very place she is standing testifying right now.
This is the baby the doctor said could not breathe.
She's alive, breathing fine, eating well, talking
and performing excellently in her academics.
She has never come second in her class; she is always first.
Hallelujah! Hallelujah!
Glory be to God!
The woman said that the baby that was dead in her womb, that the doctor said
would only come out through operation and that she could not deliver the baby
except through operation, right here at The Synagogue Church of All Nations
through the prayer of the anointed man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua,
she delivered this baby right here
and since then, the baby is living fine and she is doing fine.
Even in school, she has never come second.
Ever since she started school, she always comes first in the class.
I thank the God of T.B. Joshua for keeping me and my baby alive.
I give You all the glory and honour for Your goodness in our lives.
Thank You, God! I am very grateful!
So, she gives thanks and gives glory to God Almighty
that God Almighty is the reason why she is alive today.
He is the reason why her baby is alive. That she thanks God she did not have to go through the operation
that could have been a 50/50 chance or she would have lost her baby who was already dead in her womb.
But today she is alive, the baby is alive and she is here giving all the glory to God Almighty.
Let us put our hands together for Jesus!
Let's hear what she has to say.
My name is Mary Olomo. I want to thank God for what he has done in my life.
My mother gave birth to me at the emergency. I would like to thank Prophet T.B. Joshua
for saving me and my family
Thank you Jesus!
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!!!
So, you mean, a while ago you watched the screen,
and you saw how you jumped out from your mother's womb?
Yes.
Are you excited about that?
Right here where you are standing now?
Yes!
You can identify that that is where you standing right now?
Yes.
Let us put our hands together for Jesus!
Tell us: How old are you now?
Nine years old.
Nine years.
Your mother said that ever since you were born, you've not experienced sickness, pain,
whatever, and in your class you always come first. Is that true?
Yes.
And in what class are you now?
Primary five.
Let us put our hands together for Jesus!
Wow, that is a wonderful testimony of Mary Olomo.
With what the Lord has done in your life,
What words of advice do you have for those listening to you?
My advice for those listening to me is that they should have faith in God.
They should not lose focus on God. With faith in God, He can do anything.
Hallelujah!
Let us put our hands together for Jesus!
Our mother said that she advises everyone to believe in our Lord Jesus Christ;
that there is nothing God Almighty cannot do.
Never a sickness He cannot heal. Never a disease He cannot cure. Never a problem He cannot solve.
And never a burden He cannot bear. That any problem we think we have,
Jesus Christ is more than them and He is able to solve them.
And that she who never believed in Jesus Christ prior to the time she came to
The Synagogue Church of All Nations, because of the miracle of God in her life
she has now seen the mightiness of our Lord Jesus Christ. She has now seen and can testify
that Jesus Christ is alive. He never say goodbye to the glory of God.
Once again let us clap for Jesus!!!
So, we thank God Almighty for everything and now that God Almighty has done this in your life,
we pray that God Almighty will give you the inner grace
to make the Word of God the standard for your life
and bring up your little girl in the way of the Lord so that when she grows up,
she will not depart from it, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Hallelujah! Thank You, Jesus!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work
in our generation today and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies,
deliverances, sermons and testimonies from The Synagogue Church of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World.